OKAY. WHAT IS IT ABOUT ME?
DO I NOT LOOK FUN ENOUGH?
IS THERE SOMETHING...
REPELLENT ABOUT ME?
SO. HOW WAS THE PARTY?
WELL. IT COULDN'T
HAVE BEEN WORSE.
A WOMAN LITERALLY
PASSED THROUGH ME.
OKAY. SO WHAT IS IT?
AM I HIDEOUSLY UNATTRACTIVE?
NO. YOU ARE NOT.
YOU ARE VERY ATTRACTIVE.
YOU KNOW WHAT. I GO
THROUGH THE EXACT SAME THING.
EVERY TIME I PUT
ON A LITTLE WEIGHT
I START QUESTIONING EVERYTHING.
WHOA. WHOA.
I'VE... I'VE PUT ON
A LITTLE WEIGHT?
DID YOU WANT TO...
YEAH. UH...
NO. NOT "WEIGHT."
YOU KNOW. MORE
LIKE "INSULATION."
CHANDLER. I'M UNEMPLOYED.
IN DIRE NEED OF A PROJECT.
YOU WANT TO WORK OUT?
I-I CAN REMAKE YOU.
UH. YOU KNOW. I WOULD
BUT THAT MIGHT GET IN THE WAY
OF MY LYING AROUND TIME. SO...
PLEASE.
COME ON. LET HER DO IT.
ALL RIGHT. OKAY. ALL RIGHT
BUT IF WE PUT ON SPANDEX
AND MY BOOBS ARE
BIGGER THAN YOURS
I'M GOING HOME.
YOUR BOOBS ARE FINE.
LOOK. I NEVER SHOULD
HAVE SAID ANYTHING.
COME HERE. COME HERE.
OH... CAN'T... MAKE...
HANDS... MEET.
Captioning sponsored by
WARNER BROS. TELEVISION
♪ SO NO ONE TOLD YOU LIFE
WAS GONNA BE THIS WAY ♪
♪ YOUR JOB'S A
JOKE. YOU'RE BROKE ♪
♪ YOUR LOVE LIFE'S D.O.A. ♪
♪ IT'S LIKE YOU'RE ALWAYS
STUCK IN SECOND GEAR ♪
♪ AND IT HASN'T BEEN
YOUR DAY. YOUR WEEK ♪
♪ YOUR MONTH. OR
EVEN YOUR YEAR ♪
♪ BUT I'LL BE THERE FOR YOU ♪
♪ WHEN THE RAIN STARTS TO FALL ♪
♪ I'LL BE THERE FOR YOU ♪
♪ LIKE I'VE BEEN THERE BEFORE ♪
♪ 'CAUSE YOU'RE
THERE FOR ME TOO. ♪
OKAY...
HEY.
LET'S DO IT.
WHAT?
NOTHING. JUST NEVER SEEN YOU
IN LITTLE STRETCHY PANTS BEFORE.
IT'S CUTE.
AND WE'RE CHANGING.
♪ HEY. HEY. HEY-HEY-HEY ♪
♪ MACHO. MACHO MAN ♪
♪ MACHO MAN. YEAH ♪
♪ I'VE GOT TO BE A MACHO MAN ♪
♪ I'VE GOT TO BE A MUCHO.
MUCHO MACHO. YEAH... ♪
( groans)
COME ON. GIVE ME FIVE MORE.
FIVE MORE!
NO!
FIVE MORE AND I'LL FLASH YOU.
ONE!
TWO!
TWO AND A HALF!
OKAY. JUST SHOW ME ONE OF THEM.
♪ MACHO. MACHO MAN ♪
♪ I'VE GOT TO BE
A MACHO MAN... ♪
OW! OW! OW! OW! OW!
SHE'S INSANE.
THE WOMAN IS INSANE.
IT'S BEFORE WORK.
IT'S AFTER WORK.
IT'S DURING WORK.
SHE'S GOT ME DOING BUTT
CLENCHES AT MY DESK.
AND NOW. THEY WON'T BRING ME
MY MAIL ANYMORE.
JUST TELL HER YOU WANT TO STOP.
I CAN'T. OKAY?
WHILE SHE'S OUT OF
WORK. I'M ALL SHE'S GOT.
SO THAT'S WHY I WAS THINKING
MAYBE WE COULD ALL PITCH IN
AND BUY HER HER OWN RESTAURANT.
( door opens)
HEY. HEY. PHEEBS. HOW DID IT GO
WITH SCOTT LAST NIGHT?
OH. UM. IT WAS NICE.
TOOK HIM TO A
ROMANTIC RESTAURANT.
ORDERED CHAMPAGNE. NICE.
THE GUY STILL
WON'T PUT OUT. HUH?
NOPE. ZILCH. NOTHIN'. HUH-UH.
OH. SORRY. PHEEBS.
SORRY. PHEEBS.
LOOK. I... YOU KNOW. I
DON'T MIND TAKING IT SLOW.
I LIKE HIM A LOT.
YOU KNOW. HE'S
REALLY INTERESTING
AND HE'S REALLY SWEET AND...
WHY WON'T HE GIVE IT UP?
WELL. MAYBE HE.
UH. DRIVES HIS CAR
ON THE OTHER SIDE OF THE ROAD
IF YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN.
NO. WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
HE'S NOT BRITISH.
MAYBE HE'S GAY.
OH!
UM. NO. I DON'T THINK
THAT'S THE PROBLEM. NO.
'CAUSE WE WENT. UM.
DANCING THE OTHER NIGHT
AND JUST THE WAY
HE HELD ME SO CLOSE
AND THE WAY HE WAS
LOOKING INTO MY EYES
I JUST... I DEFINITELY
FELT SOMETHING.
YEAH. BUT HOW MUCH
CAN YOU TELL FROM A LOOK?
NO. NO. I FELT IT ON
MY HIP. I COULD TELL.
YO. BING!
RACQUETBALL IN 20 MINUTES.
JOEY. BE A PAL.
LIFT UP MY HAND AND
SMACK HER WITH IT.
OH. OH. RACHEL. DON'T LOOK.
WHAT?
COME ON. YOU GUYS. I DON'T CARE.
I HAVE A DATE TONIGHT.
WHOA. WHOA. WHOA!
YOU HAVE A DATE?
YEAH. MONICA SET ME UP.
WHAT. UH... WHAT ABOUT.
UH. ROSS AND-AND...?
WHAT. MY WHOLE
INSANE JEALOUSY THING?
HMM...
WELL. YOU KNOW. AS
MUCH FUN AS THAT WAS
I'VE DECIDED TO OPT FOR SANITY.
SO. YOU'RE REALLY
OKAY ABOUT ALL THIS?
OH. YEAH. COME
ON. I'M MOVING ON.
HE CAN PRESS HER UP
AGAINST THAT WINDOW
AS MUCH AS HE WANTS.
FOR ALL I CARE
HE CAN THROW HER
THROUGH THE DAMN THING.
HI. GUYS.
HEY. HEY.
OH. MONICA. I FIGURED I'D
COME BY TOMORROW MORNING
AND PICK UP FLUFFY'S
OLD CAT TOYS. OKAY?
ONLY IF YOU SAY HIS FULL NAME.
CAN I COME OVER TOMORROW
AND PICK UP FLUFFY
MEOWINGTON'S CAT TOYS?
ALL RIGHT.
YOU'RE GETTING A CAT?
UH. ACTUALLY.
WE'RE GETTING A CAT.
TOGETHER?
UH-HUH.
BOTH OF YOU? TOGETHER?
ROSS: YEP.
AND WE FIGURED
IT'LL LIVE WITH ROSS
HALF THE TIME AND
WITH ME HALF THE TIME.
OH. WELL. ISN'T
THAT JUST LOVELY?
THAT'S SOMETHING
THE TWO OF YOU
WILL BE ABLE TO ENJOY
FOR A REALLY. REALLY
REALLY. REALLY.
REALLY LONG TIME.
HOPEFULLY.
WELL... WHOA! LOOK AT THAT!
I GOT TO GO. I GOT A DATE.
WITH A MAN.
UM. OKAY.
YOU GUYS HAVE A REALLY.
UH... HAVE A REALLY GOOD NIGHT.
AND YOU TWO HAVE A... UH...
HAVE A. UH. REALLY GOOD CAT.
OKAY. WE'RE NOT
SUPPOSED TO TAKE THESE
WHEN WE LEAVE HERE.
I DON'T KNOW IF MONICA TOLD YOU
BUT THIS IS THE FIRST
DATE I'VE GONE ON
SINCE MY DIVORCE.
SO. IF I SEEM A LITTLE NERVOUS
I AM.
HOW LONG DO CATS LIVE?
I'M SORRY?
CATS. HOW LONG DO THEY LIVE?
FIGURING YOU DON'T. YOU KNOW
THROW THEM UNDER
A BUS OR SOMETHING.
UM... MAYBE 15. 16 YEARS.
WELL. THAT'S JUST GREAT.
UH. CHEERS!
RIGHT.
CLINK.
MONICA TOLD YOU I WAS
CUTER THAN THIS. DIDN'T SHE?
OH. NO. MICHAEL.
IT'S NOT YOU.
I'M SORRY. IT'S JUST...
IT'S THIS THING.
IT'S PROBABLY NOT
AS BAD AS IT SOUNDS
BUT THIS FRIEND OF
MINE IS-IS GETTING A CAT
WITH HIS GIRLFRIEND.
OH. THAT DOES SOUND...
HUH.
I MEAN. HE JUST STARTED
GOING OUT WITH HER.
IS THIS GUY. UH.
AN OLD BOYFRIEND?
( laughing)
YEAH. HE WISHES.
OH. I'M SORRY.
LOOK AT ME.
OKAY. MICHAEL...
LET'S TALK ABOUT YOU.
ALL RIGHT.
OKAY? OKAY.
SO...
YOU EVER GET A PET
WITH A GIRLFRIEND?
SO. I FIGURED IT OUT.
WHAT?
WHY SCOTT DOESN'T
WANT TO SLEEP WITH ME.
IT'S 'CAUSE I'M NOT SEXY ENOUGH.
OH. PHOEBE. THAT'S CRAZY.
WHEN I FIRST MET YOU
YOU KNOW WHAT I
SAID TO CHANDLER?
UH-UH.
I SAID. "EXCELLENT
BUTT. GREAT RACK."
REALLY?
THAT'S SO SWEET.
I MEAN. I'M OFFICIALLY OFFENDED
BUT IT'S SO SWEET.
PHEEBS. LOOK.
IF YOU WANT TO KNOW
WHAT THE DEAL IS
YOU'RE JUST GOING
TO HAVE TO ASK HIM.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
YOU ARE SO "YUM."
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
I MEAN. IT'S A CAT. YOU KNOW?
IT'S A... IT'S A CAT.
WHY CAN'T THEY GET
ONE OF THOSE BUGS?
YOU KNOW. ONE OF
THOSE FRUIT FLIES.
THOSE THINGS THAT LIVE
FOR. LIKE. A DAY OR SOMETHING.
WHAT ARE THEY CALLED?
FRUIT FLIES?
YES!
THANK YOU.
SO. WOULD YOU LIKE ANY DESSERT?
NO!
NO DESSERT.
JUST THE CHECK... PLEASE.
OH. NO.
YOU'RE NOT HAVING FUN. ARE YOU?
NO. NO. I AM.
BUT ONLY BECAUSE. FOR
THE LAST HOUR AND A HALF
I'VE BEEN PLAYING THE
MOVIE DINER IN MY HEAD.
OH. LOOK AT ME.
LOOK AT ME.
I'M ON A DATE WITH
A REALLY GREAT GUY.
ALL I CAN THINK ABOUT IS ROSS
AND HIS CAT
AND HIS JULIE.
LOOK. DO YOU WANT A
PIECE OF PIE OR SOMETHING?
NO!
( scoffs)
TOO LATE FOR THAT.
MAN. I'VE JUST... I'VE
SCREWED THIS ALL UP.
I JUST WANT TO GET OVER HIM.
GOD. I JUST WANT...
WHY CAN'T I DO THAT?
OY!
LOOK. I'VE BEEN
THROUGH A DIVORCE.
TRUST ME. YOU'RE
GOING TO BE FINE.
YOU JUST CAN'T SEE IT NOW
BECAUSE YOU HAVEN'T
HAD ANY CLOSURE.
OH!
CLOSURE.
THAT'S WHAT IT IS.
THAT'S WHAT I NEED.
GOD. YOU'RE BRILLIANT!
WHY DIDN'T I THINK OF
THAT? HOW DO I GET THAT?
WELL. YOU KNOW. THERE'S
NO ONE WAY. REALLY.
IT'S JUST... YOU KNOW
WHATEVER IT TAKES SO THAT
YOU CAN FINALLY SAY TO HIM
"I'M OVER YOU."
THAT'S WHAT IT IS.
CLOSURE.
OH. HELLO?
EXCUSE ME.
EXCUSE ME. HEL...
WHOA?
HANG ON.
HELLO. EXCUSE ME. HI.
WHAT?!
HI. I'M SORRY.
I NEED TO BORROW YOUR PHONE
FOR JUST ONE MINUTE.
I'M TALKING.
I CAN SEE THAT.
I... JUST ONE PHONE CALL.
I'LL BE VERY QUICK.
I'LL EVEN PAY FOR IT MYSELF.
OKAY. YOU'RE BEING A LITTLE
WEIRD ABOUT YOUR PHONE.
I'LL CALL YOU BACK.
( phone beeps)
THANK YOU.
( chuckles)
SO GOOD WITH PEOPLE.
MACHINE.
JUST WAITING FOR THE BEEP.
GOOD.
ROSS. HI.
IT'S RACHEL.
I'M JUST CALLING
TO SAY THAT... UM...
EVERYTHING'S FINE.
AND I'M REALLY HAPPY FOR YOU
AND YOUR CAT.
WHO. BY THE WAY
I THINK YOU SHOULD NAME MICHAEL.
AND. YOU KNOW. YOU SEE THERE
I'M THINKING OF NAMES
SO. OBVIOUSLY. I AM OVER YOU.
I... AM OVER...
YOU.
AND THAT. MY FRIEND
IS WHAT THEY CALL "CLOSURE."
NO. NO. NO. NO. NO
NO. NO!
MONICA. IT'S SUNDAY MORNING.
I'M NOT RUNNING ON A SUNDAY.
WHY NOT?
BECAUSE IT'S SUNDAY!
IT'S GOD'S DAY.
HEY. YOU SAY STOP. AND WE STOP.
( chuckles): OKAY!
STOP.
NO! COME ON! WE CAN'T STOP!
COME ON! WE GOT THREE
MORE POUNDS TO GO!
I AM THE ENERGY TRAIN.
AND YOU ARE ON BOARD.
( imitating train): WOO-WOO!
WOO-WOO!
WOO.
( knocking on door)
HEY. RACH.
( moans softly)
OH. AND HOW WAS THE DATE?
UM. I THINK THERE
WAS A RESTAURANT.
I KNOW THERE WAS WINE.
WOW. WELL. UH...
UH. ACTUALLY. JULIE'S
DOWNSTAIRS GETTING A CAB.
I JUST NEED
THE CAT TOYS.
DID MONICA SAY...?
WHAT. WHY... WHY ARE YOU
LOOKING AT ME LIKE THAT?
I'M SO... I DON'T KNOW.
I... I FEEL LIKE I HAD A DREAM
ABOUT YOU LAST NIGHT.
BUT... I DON'T REMEMBER.
OKAY.
OH. OH. OH.
( clears throat)
DID WE SPEAK ON THE
PHONE LAST NIGHT?
DID YOU CALL ME?
NO. I STAYED AT
JULIE'S LAST NIGHT.
HUH.
OH. ACTUALLY. I HAVEN'T
EVEN BEEN HOME YET.
DO YOU MIND IF I
CHECK MY MESSAGES?
OH. YEAH. GO AHEAD.
RACH. I GOT A MESSAGE FROM YOU.
WHO'S MICHAEL?
OH. MY GOD.
OH. MY GOD. ROSS. NO.
HANG UP THE PHONE!
GIVE ME THE PHONE. ROSS!
GIVE ME THE PHONE!
GIVE ME THE...!
YOU'RE OVER ME?
OH. GOD!
WHA...? YOU'RE. UH...
OH. GOD.
YOU'RE... YOU'RE OVER ME?
( moaning)
( softly): OH. MY GOD.
OH. GOD...
WHEN... WHEN WERE YOU...
UNDER ME?
( moaning): OH. GOD...
RACH?
RACHEL. DO YOU...?
I MEAN. WERE YOU. UH...?
( moans)
WHAT?
OKAY. OKAY. OKAY.
WELL...
BASICALLY. LATELY I'VE. UH...
( clears throat)
I'VE. UH. SORT OF HAD
FEELINGS FOR YOU.
( sighs)
YOU'VE... HAD FEELINGS FOR ME.
YEAH? WHAT? SO? YOU
HAD FEELINGS FOR ME FIRST.
WHOA! HUH.
YOU KNOW ABOUT MY...?
I MEAN. YOU KNOW I HAD...?
YOU KNOW? YOU...
CHANDLER TOLD ME.
CHANDLER. WHEN DID HE.
WHEN DID HE. WHEN DID HE?
WHEN YOU WERE IN CHINA.
CHINA.
MEETING JULIE.
JULIE. JULIE.
THAT'S... OH. GOD.
RIGHT. OKAY. I NEED TO LIE DOWN.
NO. YOU KNOW. I'M
GOING TO STAND.
I'M GOING TO STAND
AND I'M GOING TO WALK.
I'M WALKING AND...
I AM STANDING.
OKAY. SO YOU. UH...
AND NOW. WHAT... AND NOW. NOW
NOW YOU'RE OVER ME?
ARE YOU OVER ME?
( buzzer buzzes)
THAT'S... THAT'S JULIE.
THAT'S JU... JULIE.
JULIE!
HI. JULIE!
Hi. honey. I've
got a cab waiting.
I'LL BE RIGHT DOWN.
WAIT. SO. YOU'RE GOING?
WELL. OKAY. I. UH. I HAVE TO.
I CAN'T DEAL WITH
THIS RIGHT NOW.
I MEAN. I'VE. UH... YOU
KNOW. I'VE GOT A CAB.
I'VE GOT A GIRLFRIEND.
I'M-I'M GOING TO GO GET A CAT.
OKAY. OKAY.
CAT.
( singing in Hebrew)
HEY. JOEY.
HEY. PHEEBS.
( playing solo)
HOW COME YOU'RE WATCHING
A RABBI PLAY ELECTRIC GUITAR?
I CAN'T FIND THE REMOTE.
OH. THANK YOU.
SO SCOTT ASKED ME
TO COME OVER FOR
LUNCH TODAY. AND I DID.
AND..?
AND WE DID.
ALL RIGHT. PHEEBS!
WAY TO GO!
YAY ME.
SO... SO HOW DID IT HAPPEN?
WELL. I FINALLY TOOK YOUR ADVICE
AND ASKED HIM WHAT WAS GOING ON.
AND WHAT DID HE SAY?
HE SAID HE UNDERSTANDS
HOW SEX CAN BE. LIKE. A VERY
EMOTIONAL THING FOR A WOMAN
AND HE WAS JUST AFRAID
THAT I WAS GOING TO GET
ALL. YOU KNOW. LIKE
"OOH. IS-HE-GOING-TO-CALL-ME
THE-NEXT-DAY?"
AND. YOU KNOW.
"WHERE-IS-THIS-GOING?"
BLAH-BLAH-BLAH... YEAH...
HE SAID HE WANTED TO HOLD OFF
UNTIL HE WAS PREPARED
TO BE REALLY SERIOUS.
WOW.
YEAH. SO I SAID.
"OKAY. RELAX. PLEASE."
YOU KNOW?
I MEAN
SEX CAN BE JUST ABOUT
TWO PEOPLE RIGHT THERE
IN THE MOMENT. YOU KNOW.
IF HE WANTS TO SEE
ME AGAIN. HE CAN CALL
AND IF NOT. THAT'S FINE. TOO.
SO AFTER A LOT OF TALKING...
I CONVINCED HIM.
L-LET ME GET THIS STRAIGHT:
HE GOT YOU TO BEG
TO SLEEP WITH HIM.
HE GOT YOU TO SAY HE
NEVER HAS TO CALL YOU AGAIN
AND...
HE GOT YOU THINKING
THIS IS A GREAT IDEA?
UH-HUH.
THIS MAN IS MY GOD.
OOH. THIS ONE'S
CUTE. DON'T YOU THINK?
YEAH. THIS ONE'S CUTE
AND-AND THAT ONE'S
CUTE. AND THAT ONE'S CUTE.
THEY'RE ALL CUTE.
THEY'RE KITTENS.
LET'S JUST WRAP ONE UP AND
GET THE HELL OUT OF HERE.
YOU OKAY?
YEAH. ME? ME?
SURE. YEAH. YEAH. YEAH.
ROSS. HONEY. HEY.
I KNOW THAT THIS
IS A BIG STEP FOR US
BUT I'VE GOT A FEELING
WE'RE GOING TO BE OKAY.
YEAH. I KNOW. I KNOW.
SO. UM. DO YOU HAVE ANY
CATS THAT ARE REALLY OLD
OR INCREDIBLY SICK?
ROSS? HUH?
I DON'T WANT ONE
THAT'S ABOUT TO DIE.
OH. SEE. NOW WE SHOULD
HAVE WORKED THAT OUT
BEFORE WE CAME DOWN HERE.
OKAY. SWEETIE. I'M GOING
TO NARROW IT DOWN
TO THIS ONE OVER HERE...
YEAH.
AND THIS ONE WITH
THE STRIPES. OKAY?
UH-HUH. YEAH.
YOU PICK.
OH. HMM. WHOA. HEY
I. UH. I HAVE TO PICK?
YEAH. WHICHEVER ONE YOU WANT.
( cats meowing softly)
WELL. I. UM...
I DON'T KNOW!
I MEAN. IT'S NOT THAT EASY
TO CHOOSE. YOU KNOW?
I MEAN. BOTH-BOTH CATS
ARE-ARE-ARE BEAUTIFUL AND. UM...
( sighs)
FUNNY AND...
YOU KNOW. I-I'M SURE I'D
BE HAPPY WITH EITHER CAT.
I JUST...
WELL. DO YOU WANT TO TAKE BOTH?
BOTH?! BOTH?!
I CAN'T HAVE TWO CATS! I MEAN...
JOEY'S THE KIND OF GUY
WHO COULD HAVE TWO CATS.
GOOD NIGHT. GUNTHER.
( gasping): HI.
I DIDN'T GET A CAT.
OH. THAT'S. UM...
INTERESTING.
NO. NO. IT'S NOT
INTERESTING. OKAY?
IT'S VERY. VERY NOT INTERESTING.
IT'S ACTUALLY 100% COMPLETELY
THE OPPOSITE OF INTERESTING.
I GOT IT. ROSS.
YOU HAD NO RIGHT TO TELL ME
YOU EVER HAD FEELINGS FOR ME.
WHAT?!
I WAS DOING GREAT WITH JULIE
BEFORE I FOUND OUT ABOUT YOU.
HEY. I WAS DOING GREAT
YOU THINK IT'S EASY FOR
ME TO SEE YOU WITH JULIE?
WELL. THEN YOU SHOULD HAVE
SAID SOMETHING BEFORE I MET HER!
I DIDN'T KNOW THEN!
AND HOW COME YOU
NEVER SAID ANYTHING TO ME?
THERE WAS NEVER A GOOD TIME.
RIGHT! BECAUSE
YOU ONLY HAD A YEAR
AND WE ONLY HUNG
OUT EVERY NIGHT.
NOT... NOT... NOT...
EVERY NIGHT.
YOU KNOW
AND-AND IT'S NOT LIKE
I DIDN'T TRY. RACHEL
BUT THINGS GOT IN THE WAY
YOU KNOW. LIKE-LIKE ITALIAN GUYS
OR EX-FIANCEES
OR. OR. OR...
ITALIAN GUYS.
HEY. THERE WAS ONE
ITALIAN GUY. OKAY?
AND DO YOU EVEN HAVE A POINT?
THE POINT IS I... I DON'T
NEED THIS RIGHT NOW. OKAY?
IT'S-IT'S TOO LATE. I'M
WITH SOMEBODY ELSE.
I'M HAPPY. THIS SHIP HAS SAILED.
OKAY. SO WHAT ARE YOU SAYING?
YOU CAN JUST
SORT OF PUT AWAY FEELINGS
OR WHATEVER THE HELL IT
WAS THAT YOU FELT FOR ME?
HEY. I'VE BEEN DOING IT
SINCE THE NINTH GRADE.
I'VE GOTTEN PRETTY
DAMN GOOD AT IT.
ALL RIGHT. FINE. YOU GO AHEAD
AND YOU DO THAT. ALL
RIGHT. ROSS? FINE. FINE.
'CAUSE I DON'T NEED
YOUR STUPID SHIP!
GOOD.
AND YOU KNOW WHAT?
NOW I GOT CLOSURE!
OH!
( frustrated sigh)
( sobbing softly)
( rattling door)
TRY THE BOTTOM ONE.
MONICA. IT'S 6:30
IN THE MORNING.
WE'RE NOT WORKING OUT.
IT'S OVER.
NO WAY! WITH ONE
POUND TO GO? COME ON!
♪ WE'RE WORKING ♪
♪ WE'RE MOVING ♪
♪ WE'RE IN THE ZONE.
WE'RE GROOVING. ♪
OKAY. I DON'T... I DON'T
MIND THE LAST POUND. OKAY?
IN FACT. I KIND OF
LIKE THE LAST POUND.
OKAY? SO DON'T MAKE ME
DO ANYTHING THAT I'LL REGRET.
OH! WHAT YOU GOING
TO DO. FAT BOY? HUH?
WHAT?
NOTHING. EXCEPT TELL YOU.
UH. I THINK IT'S WONDERFUL
HOW MUCH ENERGY YOU HAVE.
WELL! THANKS.
I MEAN
ESPECIALLY CONSIDERING
HOW TOUGH IT'S BEEN
FOR YOU TO FIND WORK.
WELL. YOU KNOW. YOU...
YOU KNOW. I MEAN
YOU CAN'T TELL YOUR
PARENTS YOU WERE FIRED
BECAUSE THEY'D BE DISAPPOINTED.
UH-HUH.
AND IT'S NOT AS IF YOU HAVE
A BOYFRIEND'S
SHOULDER TO CRY ON.
WELL. NO. BUT. I...
I MEAN. IF IT WERE ME
I THINK I'D HAVE DIFFICULTY
JUST GETTING OUT OF BED AT ALL.
YOU KNOW. I TRY
TO STAY POSITIVE.
SO. YOU...
YOU FEEL LIKE GOING FOR A RUN?
ALL RIGHT.
BECAUSE. YOU KNOW.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO.
IF YOU WANT. YOU COULD
JUST TAKE A NAP RIGHT HERE.
OKAY.
JUST FOR A LITTLE WHILE.
Captioned by Media Access
Group at WGBH access.wgbh.org
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm